Guide to the William Hillman Shockley Photographs, 1896-1922 and undated, bulk 1897-1909 RL.01177
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- China: Manchuria, 1897-1898; 337 prints
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0440)
    Chinese servant Kuei To with black hat and formal dress, standing side view
    中国仆人Kuei，头戴黑帽，着正装侧身像
  - Manchurian Inn, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0441)
    满洲客栈
  - Yang [the Liar ?], circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0442.1)
    [杨，撒谎者？]
  - Yang [the Liar ?], circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0442.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0442.1
  - Yang [the Liar ?], circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0442.3)
  - Magpies, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0443)
    喜鹊
  - Bull fight, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0444)
    斗架的牛
  - Chinese soldier, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0445.1)
    中国士兵， [抬枪]
  - Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0445.2)
    中国士兵，
    Chinese soldier
    抬枪
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0445.1
  - Salt Lake, LuT'sun, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0446.1)
    盐湖 LuT'sun
  - Salt Lake, LuT'sun, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0446.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0446.1
  - Salt Lake LuT'sun, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0446.3)
  - Lao [Yuig?] Kou Trip, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0447)
    老峪沟 [？]之旅
  - Sai Wa Chi, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0448)
    Saiwaji
  - Lead mine, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0449)
  - Lead mine, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0450)
  - Manchu Caravan, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0452)
    满洲，马队
  - Inn sign. Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0453)
    客栈的招牌，满洲
  - Local Soldier, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0454.1)
    地方团练，满洲
  - Local Soldier, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0454.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0454.1
  - Local Soldier, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0454.3)
  - Manchurian Soldier, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0455)
    满洲士兵
    version of RL01177-P-445.1
  - Inn yard Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0456)
    客栈的院子，满洲
  - Chinese Inn in Manchuria?, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0457)
    客栈，满洲？
  - Manchurian Sheep, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0458.1)
    [羊，满洲]
  - Manchurian Sheep, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0458.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0458.1
  - Inn at Moukden, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0459)
    沈阳的旅店
  - Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0460)
    People standing in front of house
    人们站在屋前
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0461.1)
    Men riding horses
    骑马的人们
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0461.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0461.1
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0462)
    Caravan traveling
    商旅马队
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0463)
    Horses on field
    田野中的马
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0464)
    Horse at inn yard ?
    客栈的庭院中的马
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0465)
    Men on horses
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0466)
    Hillside
    山侧
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0467)
    Man on horse in field
    田间骑马的人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0468)
    City wall
    城墙
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0469)
    Bridge on river through city wall
    城门，城墙和护城河上的桥
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0470)
    Bridge on river
    河上的桥
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0471)
    Buildings
    建筑
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0472)
    Building
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0473)
    Statue and building
    神像 & 建筑
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0474)
    Overlooking courtyard
    俯瞰庭院
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0475)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0476)
    Cart wheel
    车轮
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0477)
    Adults and children in front of a gate and palisade
    站在庭院门前的一群人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0478)
    Crowd in front of an inn?
    客栈门前的人群 ?
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0479)
    客栈外的人群 ?
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0480)
    Korean woman carrying baby
    韓國女子攜帶的嬰兒
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0481)
    Man standing beside a censer
    香炉边的男人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0482)
    Man working in field
    田间劳动者
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0483)
    Watchtower on hill
    山坡上的瞭望塔楼
  - Kao Li / Mutzu, 1897 October 20 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0484.1)
    Haystack?
    草垛
  - Kao Li / Mutzu, 1897 October 20 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0484.2)
    duplicate of Rl01177-P-0484.1
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0485)
    田间的劳动者
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0486)
    Field
    田间
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0487)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0488)
    Mountain and field
    山野
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0489)
    Overlook of fields
    远眺田野
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0490)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0491)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0492)
    Mountain valley
    山谷
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0493)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0494)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0495)
    Mountain valley and river
    山谷河流
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0496.1)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0496.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0496.1
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0497.1)
    Overlook from mountain
    从山上俯瞰
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0497.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0497.1
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0498)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0499)
    Man and horses below a cliff
    山崖下的人与马
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0500)
    Boats parked by a river
    河边停靠的船只
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0501)
    Two men and a horse near a river
    河边的两个男人和一匹马
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0502)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0503)
    View of river
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0504)
    Koreans carrying a sedan chair
    抬着轿子的朝鲜人
  - Korean boy, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0505.1)
    朝鲜男孩
    This child seems to also appear in P-0386.
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0505.2)
    Koreans standing around a pile of straw
    围在稻草堆的一群朝鲜人
    May be children in setting found in P-0386.
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0505.1
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0506)
    Korean man walking in a village street
    朝鲜男子走在村里的街道
  - Koreans, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0507)
    Korean children
    朝鲜儿童
  - Inn yard Manchuria 1898 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0511)
    客栈的院子，1898年
  - Korean workings, old pit, Hsing Lung Kou, 1897 April 27 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0857)
    朝鲜族，在田野劳作，兴隆沟4月27日
    538
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0858)
    Woman in doorway breastfeeding baby
    version of RL01177-P-0385.1
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0859)
    Several men with horses in field
    幾名男子與馬在外地
  - Gravel Mining / Je Shui?, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0860)
    矿石开采, 1897年 / Je Shui?
  - W.H. Shockley, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0861.1)
    肖克利
    On horse
  - W.H. Shockley, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0861.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0861.1
  - W.H. Shockley, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0861.3)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0862)
    Possibly a school Interior with boys (and teacher) sitting at a table?
    私塾内的孩童(和老师)围坐在桌旁?
  - Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0863)
    People with flags in field
    打着旗子走在田间的人们
  - Valley of the Yalu, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0864)
    鸭绿江河谷
  - Temple on Wall. Moukden, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0865)
    城墙上的寺庙，沈阳，1897
  - Road of Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0866)
    沈阳城外道路
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0867)
    Person selling fruit (sugar coated haws?) on sticks
    卖糖葫芦的人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0868)
    Wealthy Chinese family
    富人一家
  - Moukden [Street], 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0869)
    沈阳街道, 1897
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0870)
    Woman holding baby
    抱孩子的妇女
  - Manchu Emperor Tomb, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0871)
    清皇陵
  - Moukden, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0872)
    沈阳
    Dwellings next to large city walls
    紧挨城墙的一排棚屋
  - Mukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0873)
    People and tower
    塔前的几个人
  - Liu En and friend, Moukden, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0874)
    刘鹗夫妇，沈阳，1897
    Man sitting next to young woman
  - Priest's house, Lama temple, Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0875)
    藏传佛教寺庙，僧侣住所，沈阳
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0876)
    Man with bow in courtyard
    练习射箭的男子
  - Pagoda at Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0877)
    沈阳佛塔
  - Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0878)
    Memorial arch
    牌坊
  - Landlady near Huai Jeu Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0879)
    房东太太，满洲怀仁县 [现桓仁满族自治县]附近
  - A Korean boy near Yalu river, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0880)
    朝鲜族男孩，鸭绿江附近，1897
    Same boy as in other images, P-0386, P-0505.
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0881)
    Woman in house
    屋中的妇女
  - Inn of Fu Men Tzu, Oct 26, 1897 October 26 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0882.1)
    土门子的客栈 10月26日
    Man smoking
    吸烟的男子
  - Inn of Fu Men Tzu, Oct 26, 1897 October 26 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0882.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0882.1
  - Inn of Fu Men Tzu, Oct 26, 1897 October 26 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0882.3)
  - Moukden druggist, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0883)
    药材商，沈阳
  - Shrines, Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0884)
    祭坛，满州，1897
  - No known title, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0885)
    Workmen
    干活的人
  - Paying for coat, Moukden, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0886)
    买毛皮，沈阳，1897
  - Iron furnace at Sai Ma Chi, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0887)
    炼铁炉，赛马镇，满州
  - Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0888)
    Part of a building
    建筑物部分
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0889)
    Man with a falcon
    训鹰的男子
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0890)
  - Servant Kuei To, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0891)
    贵铎仆从
  - Oolah, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0892)
    Small boy with large pestle sitting on ground pounding grass
    小男孩坐在地上拿着大锤锤草
  - Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0893)
    Sheep in farmyard
    院子里的羊
  - Kuei To, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0894)
    贵铎
    Same man as in later shots: P-0891, P-0894
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0895)
    North Tomb (Zhaoling) of Qing emperor, now in Beiling Park, northern Shenyang
    清北陵，沈阳
  - Inn yard, Kuan Tien Hsieu, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0896)
    客栈的院子，宽甸县
  - Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0897)
  - Kaoliang Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0898)
    高粱地，满州
    Kaoliang (millet)
  - Yalu River, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0899)
    鸭绿江
  - Hun River, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0900)
    浑江
  - Well of Moukden, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0901)
    水井，沈阳，满州
  - An Enricher of China, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0902)
    施肥的人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0907)
    River in valley
    山谷中的河流
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0908)
    Women and children in front yard
    屋前的妇女和孩童
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0910)
    (Chinese?) woman on horse with servant leading
    骑马的(中国?)妇女，前面有仆人牵引
  - Hun River Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0911)
    浑江，满州
  - Near Huai Jen Hsien Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0912)
  - Hun River, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0913)
  - Huai Jen Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0914)
  - Kuan Tien Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0915)
    宽甸县
  - Dr. Westwater's house, Liao Yang, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0916)
    韦斯特沃特博士的房子，辽阳，满州
    Westwater was a physician and missionary and resided for many years in Liaoyang.
  - Pass between / Huai Jen Hsien / Kuan Tien Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0917)
    怀仁县宽甸县交界处
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0918)
    Men, horses, and wagons
    马车队
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0919)
    Soldiers carrying a gun
    士兵抬枪
  - Yalu River, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0920)
    View of mountain valley
    河谷
  - Weaver, Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0921)
    织布，满州
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0922)
    Man in front of fence
    篱笆墙前的男子
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0923)
    Shrine
    祭坛
  - Inn in Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0924)
    客栈，满州
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0925)
    Inn sign
    客栈的招牌
    version of RL01177-P-0453
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0926)
    Children on rail fence
    篱笆墙上的孩子
  - Accident in Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0927)
    马车翻倒，满州
    Wagon turned over while crossing river
    过河时马车被卡住
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0928)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0930)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0931)
    River rushing over rocks
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0933)
    River rapids
  - Main road near Moukden, Manchuria, Oct. 1897, 1897 October (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0934)
    沈阳附近主路10月
  - Near Tai P'ing [Sai?], circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0935)
    太平 [寨？] 附近
  - Ginseng cultivation, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0936)
    种人参
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0937)
    Pigs feeding off a millstone
    猪吃磨盘上的粮食
  - Frontier meeting / Korea and China / Yalu River, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0938)
    鸭绿江边的聚会 / 朝鲜和中国
  - Manchu emperor tombs, view thru the gate, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0939)
    入口处远眺清帝陵
  - Liao Yang, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0940)
    White Tower
    白塔
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0941)
    Lion statue, probably in Liao Yang
    石狮
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0942)
    Village with White Pagoda in distance
    村庄和远处的佛塔
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0943)
    Two men in a field with a pig
    田里两个男子和一头猪
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0944)
    People in front of a horsecart
    马车前的人们
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0945)
    Man on horseback in shallow water
    骑马的人站在浅水中
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0946)
    Man crouched in front of a brick wall
    蹲在砖墙前的人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0947)
    View upward from the inside of a pagoda
    塔内向上望
  - Ahden [____?] Pigeon Shoot [?], circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0948)
    Crouching man with long rifle
    蹲着打枪的男子
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0949)
    View of a cliff face
    崖面
  - Gold rush, Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0951)
    淘金，满州
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0952)
    Gated yard and a hilltop compound
    有围墙的院落和山包上的房屋
  - Chinese Servant [?], circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0953)
    Kuei To
    Same man with black hat as RL01177-P-0891 and P-0894
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0954)
    Chinese officials group photo
    清朝官员合影
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0955)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0956)
    Two men in front of a stone structure (furnace?)
    两人站在石头建筑（炉子？）前
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0957)
    Man leading a horse
    男子牵着一匹马
  - Near Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0958)
  - Chieh Lui K'ou May, 1897 May (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0959)
    1897年5月
  - Servant of Kuei To, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0960.1)
    Man on horseback with rifle
    骑在马上用枪瞄准
  - Servant of Kuei To, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0960.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0960.1
  - Kaoliang [on cart] Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0961)
    [车上的]高粱，满州
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0962)
    Western man walking on a muddy sidewalk
    外国男子走在泥泞的人行道上
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0963)
    Men and carts at the foot of a mountain
    山脚下的马车队
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0964)
    Women standing in a doorway under thatched roofing
    站在茅屋门口的妇女
  - Drum, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0965)
    鼓
    Includes Chinese children and one man looking at camera
    一名男子和孩童们
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0966)
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0967)
    Person under awning in a doorway
    站在茅草屋檐下的人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0968)
    Men gathered inside an inn
    客栈屋内的几个人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0969)
    Men and horses on a mountain path
    山路上的马队
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0970.1)
    Cylindrical cone-roofed granary
    尖顶粮仓
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0970.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0970.1
  - Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0971)
    Horse and cart in the opening of a brick wall
    砖墙豁口处的马车
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0972)
    Man and horse on a plain
    田野中牵马的人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0973)
    Falconer and several men looking at camera
    几个男子，一人架鹰
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0974)
    Two men sitting on a bed
    坐在炕上的两人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0975)
    Man in front with onlookers behind a fence, Korean
    男子及草垛后的众人，朝鲜族
  - Valley of Liao River near Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0976)
    辽河岸边，靠近沈阳
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0977)
    Two lion statues guarding a closed door
    关着的大门前的两只石狮子
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0978)
    Korean boy shielding eyes from the sun
    朝鲜男孩用手遮挡阳光
  - Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0979)
  - Near T'ai Ping Sai / Quartzite bluffs in fog / Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0980)
    太平寨附近/雾中的山崖/满州
  - Near Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0981)
    Men and horse carts
    马队
  - Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0982)
    满州 ,1897年
    Children on a fence
    篱笆上的几个孩童
    version of RL01177-P-0926
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0984)
    Geese near a wall
    墙边的几只鹅
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0950)
    School, Manchuria?
    学校，满州 ?
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0985.1)
    Youth and old man in a crowd, Korean
    人群中的老人和女孩，朝鲜族
    The youth and old man may also appear in image 950.
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0985.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0985.1
  - School, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0986)
    学校，满州
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0987)
    Carts parked in the yard of an inn
    客栈院子里的车
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0988)
    Western man posing in a doorway
    外国男子站在屋门口
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0989)
    Boat trackers towing the boat
    拉纤的纤夫们
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0990.1)
    Man in horse-drawn cart with attendants
    坐在马车里的男子和他的仆从
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0990.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-0990.1
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0991)
    Family standing in a yard
    院中的几个人
  - Ferry on Hun River, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0992)
    浑江上的渡船
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0993)
    View of a large yard
    一个大院子
  - Bent strata, Jen Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0994)
    弯曲的岩石，怀仁县
    Geological layers visible behind man on horseback in field
    田野中骑马的男子背景中
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0995)
    Boats sailing on a river
    江中的船只
  - Kaoliang or Millet, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0997)
    高粱堆或者粟堆旁
    People standing next to tall sheaves
    人们站在高粱堆旁
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0998)
    Boats near the riverbank
    靠近江边的船
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-0999)
    Animal statue
    动物塑像
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1000)
    Man with rifle on horseback
    背着枪骑着马的男子
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1001)
    Village along the river
    江边的村庄
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1002)
    Several boats along the riverbank
    江边停靠的几只船
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1003)
    Man on a post jutting out over the river
    男子站在江边突出到水上的支架上
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1004)
    Men on boats by the riverside
    江边的船，船上的人
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1005)
    Boats lined up along a waterway
    水面上停靠的一排船
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1006)
    Structure on riverbank
    岸边建筑
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1007)
    Men towing boats from the riverside
    纤夫们在岸上拉纤
  - Mts. near Kuai Tien Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1008)
    宽甸县附近的山
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1009)
    Single boat sailing the water
    江面上的一只船
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1010)
    Pagoda
  - Pounding grass for stockings, Manchuria, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1011)
    两个男子做草编，满州
  - Top of pass / Huai Jen Hsien Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1012)
    关口顶部 / 怀仁县 [现桓仁满族自治县] /满州 /1897年
    Two Chinese with backpacks
    两位中国与背包
  - Dagoba near Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1013)
    沈阳附近的舍利塔
    Distant view of pagoda
    宝塔远景
  - Kuei To Manchuria, 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1014)
    贵铎，满州
    Kuei To on pony
    小馬
  - No known title, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1015)
    Western-style large church
    西式教堂建筑
  - Shockley, Manchuria, 1897 December (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1016)
    肖克利，满州12月
  - Granite mts. near Moukden to Railway, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1017)
    岩石山，沈阳附近通向铁路
  - Manchuria / Shuo?, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1018)
    City view
    城景
  - Gate / Moukden / Tombs of emperors, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1019)
    沈阳，皇陵大门
  - Huai Jen Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1020)
    怀仁县 [现桓仁满族自治县]
  - Bent strata, Huai Jen Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1021)
    弯曲的岩石, 怀仁县 [现桓仁满族自治县]
  - Huai Jen Hsien, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1022)
  - Hun River, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1023)
  - Dr. Ross & Wife & boy / Moukden, circa 1897 (Box 3, Print RL01177-P-1024)
    罗恩博士与妻子和儿子 / 沈阳
    Dr. John Ross was a physician and a Scottish Presbyterian missionary.